labome.com 2017-06-06

# Labome Privacy Statement

Labome Privacy Statement

Synatom Research, the provider of Labome website, provides free searching services for biomedical research communities. We do **not** collect personal information about you when you visit Labome website unless you choose to provide that information to us.

Of the information we learn about you from your visit to Labome website, we store only the following: the IP address from which you access the Internet, the date and time, the Internet address of the Website from which you linked directly to our site, the names of files or words you searched, and the browser used to access our site. This information is used to measure the number of visitors to various sections of our site and identify system performance or problem areas. We also use this information to help us expand the coverage of reagents and other information, and to make the site more useful. Occasionally, we provide this information to third party entities to generate better and more timely antibodies and other products. 

A "cookie" is a small file that a Web site transfers to your computer's hard disk allowing our server to "remember" specific information about your session. We use cookies in Labome website to speed up your search. The only information in our cookies is an ID number if your browser is set to accept cookies.

If you choose to provide us with personal information by sending an email, or by filling out a form with your personal information and submitting it through our Web site, we use that information to complete your request. Your contact information may be shared with third parties, if we consider such third parties may be able to provide products or services that fulfill your requests.

We provide links to other Internet sites that provide various information. Once you link to another site, you are subject to the privacy policy and copyright of the new site.

Synatom Research, the provider of Labome website maintains this site. For site security purposes and to ensure that this service remains available to all users, we use software programs to monitor traffic to identify unauthorized attempts to upload or change information, or otherwise cause damage. We may refuse to service a specific IP address, if we deem necessary.
